Dazhuang
You went in there and got nothing on camera?
Master
You really fell asleep.
Went in there and got nothing on camera.
What happened after you entered the ER?
At first, a doctor came to examine me.
Then they started an IV drip.
My eyelids kept getting heavier and heavier.
Finally, I just couldn't fight it.
And I fell asleep.
And then?
And then I ended up kneeling here.
Master, what step did I get wrong?
Get up first.
Li Xiande's exposure put them on alert.
The experiment's been terminated.
So what do we do?
There's another possibility.
We got Master Zhang from Lijia Village,
and sent Li Qiankun in.
The Wang Family lost their herb supplier.
New drug production can't keep up.
So the experiment naturally stopped.
But whatever the reason,
we can't get in there to find evidence.
No.
We still have one option.
Lure the snake out of its hole.
Ren Feifan has been kicked out, right?
Yes.
I had the board make it effective that day.
Well done.
Kill two birds with one stone.
Have you picked the new herb suppliers?
Most categories are already chosen.
Supplies are already coming in.
The rest will be secured in two weeks.
There shouldn't be any issue.
What about the new drug?
Without the Li Family,
secured Aconite and Pinellia Rhizome?
Not yet.
I found some herb growers in remote areas.
It's poor there, and nobody checks.
With enough money as bait,
there shouldn't be any issue.
But...
What is it?
Herb masters are hard to find now.
Growing those herbs is officially banned.
So few masters can process them properly.
For the time being,
it's hard to find one
who can process them to the old standard.
Dad, are you all right?
You've been coughing for a while.
I'm fine.
What matters is the new drug.
We've bet most of our fortune on it.
Only if it delivers results
will our investment not go to waste.
The herb master...
Find one as soon as possible.
Yes.
The Princess of Xinai is in North City.
I hear although Xinai is a small country,
its royal family is super rich.
And this Princess of Xinai
is a disciple of Xinai's Medicine King.
A princess and a disciple. Impressive.
Wonder what brings her to North City.
What else could it be?
North City is the Medicine Capital.
She's here to expand her business.
Probably.
Dad, look at this.
It fell right into my lap.
Without any effort at all.
The Princess of Xinai.
I hear this Princess of Xinai
has an incredibly powerful medical team.
This trip to North City
is for a technical exchange with us.
That's great.
I'll get some gifts and visit her.
Mm.
I'm Wang Wenhao of North City Wang Group.
I'm here to see the Princess of Xinai.
We have an appointment.
Mr. Wang, please cooperate.
Search him.
Please.
Hello, Princess.
I'm Wang Wenhao from the Wang Group.
I brought you a gift.
Pleasure to meet you, Mr. Wang.
I've heard of Wang's medicines in Xinai.
It's a great honor.
Please, have a seat.
Having you visit North City
is truly an honor for our city.
The Wang Group officially welcomes you.
I hear you enjoy floral tea, Princess.
Mr. Wang.
My time is precious.
And I'm sure yours is too.
If you're only here to deliver a gift,
I've already received it.
You may take your leave now.
Here's the thing, Princess.
The Wang Group is developing a new drug.
Once launched, its potential is limitless.
I've heard your pharmaceutical team
is highly professional.
So I'm here to discuss a partnership.
You want me to help produce your new drug?
It's not a one-sided request.
It's mutually beneficial, of course.
This new drug of ours
is based on an ancient formula,
developed into a miracle cure.
The formula is risky and unconventional.
But once it succeeds,
the benefits will last for generations.
Oh?
What kind of risky formula?
Aconite and Pinellia Rhizome.
But as far as I know,
these herbs are banned in your country
from being grown or sold.
Seems you're quite bold, Mr. Wang.
But with herbs, a miss is as good as a mile.
So before we partner up,
I'd like to request, Princess,
that we first produce some samples.
No problem.
But these herbs...
I'll deliver them as soon as possible.
But please understand, Princess,
these herbs are restricted in our country.
What I mean is,
I already have all these herbs.
All of them?
Mm-hm.
These herbs are restricted here,
but not in Xinai.
That's wonderful, Princess.
Then I'll await your good news.
I'll take my leave now.
The Wang Family took the bait.
You can start producing the new samples.
My dear junior brother.
This Wang Wenhao is really cunning.
Thought we'd prove he bought banned drugs.
But after all that runaround,
the Xu Family ended up signing instead.
I don't need proof of illegal drug buying.
I need to enter his human experiment lab.
Try on a few more outfits.
Last time when you were hospitalized,
Wenhao said he didn't have time.
Come on.
Their family paid all your medical bills.
You must go thank them now.
Hurry, pick out a few more.
Choose something nice.
Mom,
I don't want to try them on.
And I'm not going.
I want to call off the engagement.
Did you hit your head or something?
He's Wang Wenhao!
The only son of the Wang Group.
Many North City girls want to marry him.
And let me tell you,
Yesterday, I signed a contract for Wenhao.
With the Princess of Xinai.
Wang Wenhao and the Princess made a deal.
The Princess is noble and vastly wealthy.
Both an aristocrat and a businesswoman.
Once he's tied to her,
Wenhao's fortune will be beyond measure.
Listen to me, forget about Ren Feifan.
Mom,
Do you know why I recovered so fast?
Feifan saved me.
He came to give me acupuncture that night.
I saw him.
I've read my medical records.
My injuries were severe.
Only his Eight Ghost Acupuncture saved me.
But that technique shortens his lifespan.
Isn't it his duty to save you?
You got hurt because of him.
He's just expecting favors in return.
A rat from the gutter.
He just won't go away.
Mom,
I already owe him too much.
Anyway, I'm not marrying Wang Wenhao.
Go tell Ren Feifan to come out here.
Ren Feifan!
I've never met anyone so shameless.
You just won't go away.
I'm warning you,
Stop harassing our Ruojin.
A filthy stinking rat from the gutter,
trying to snag a rich flower.
Our Ruojin
is going to marry Wang Wenhao.
She'll be the Wang Group chairman's wife.
You shouldn't even dream of it.
Oh, Princess!
Princess, why are you here?
You remember me, right?
I'm Zeng Meihua, the group rep.
You remember, don't you?
The one who signed the contract yesterday.
I was just curious.
Since my junior is a rat from the gutter,
so I came out to take a look.
If he's a rat from the gutter,
then what does that make me,
his senior?
This...
Feifan.
Princess, I didn't mean it that way.
I didn't know you and Feifan were...
Save your excuses.
Take a look at the contract first.
It contains banned substances.
This...
This, this, this can't be.
Wenhao wouldn't harm our family like this.
You're truly blind to the truth.
It's written clearly in black and white.
Your signature is right here.
Aconite and Pinellia Rhizome are banned.
This contract will put you behind bars.
Feifan, please help Auntie.
You'll save me, won't you?
Won't you?
After all, you and Ruojin are...
I can withhold the evidence,
but Auntie, you must promise me two things.